Hello everyone, welcome to the series of classes to learn Cloth newbie entry
if you are interested in 3D fashion design, but lack of basic, lack of direction
this course is for you to create
this course will lead you from scratch
systematic processing of 3D fashion modeling core logic
to help you quickly cross the newbie threshold
really use this powerful tool for you
First of all, I will introduce you to Cloth account registration and installation
You can enter the website cloth3d-china.com
enter the official website in China
You can also unlock Cloth 3D or Cloth Chinese official website in the browser
Come to the official website, click on the login in the upper right corner
In the login page, click on the registration button in the lower right corner
Select personal and student user registration
Note that the Cloth site account is registered here
You can use the same account to log in all Cloth products without error
such as Cloth software, Cloth site platform and connect merchant, etc.
Enter your email and mobile phone number to complete the Cloth site account registration
Complete mobile phone verification
You can choose by personal needs
Push the email of the relevant product at the bottom of the page
Then click on the create account
According to the prompt, go to the mailbox to complete the verification
This way, the Cloth account is registered
By email verification, it will automatically jump to the Cloth Chinese official website
At this time, the account has been logged in
You can click on the image in the upper right corner to check the account
You can also click on the exit login
Re-login other accounts
After registration, you can see the free trial in the upper right corner
New users have 14 days free trial of Cloth software
Click on the download button
You will come to the download page of the Cloth installation package
You need to use your computer system
Mac system or Windows system
To choose to download the installation package
Because 3D modeling has certain requirements for computer performance
Before downloading the installation
You can click on the bottom right corner
Check the computer configuration requirements
Ensure that the software can be used normally after installation
After confirming the computer configuration
Go back to the download page
Download the Cloth installation package
Wait for the download to be completed
This is the downloaded Cloth installation package
On the top right, you can choose to run as a manager
Follow the video steps to complete the installation
I recommend that you must install it under the C drive
Finally, click finish
Here will pop up the explanation of the update and repair function of the Cloth version
Just click close
After installation
Find the Cloth software icon on the desktop
Double-click to open the software
First start
You need to agree to the service terms
Click Yes
Log in again
Click Sign in with Clothset to log in with Clothset
In the pop-up page
Enter the email account and password you just registered
After logging in, it will show that you have now logged in Clothset
You can return to Cloth to continue
At this time, Cloth will also pop up the login window
When installing the login for the first time
In the initial settings
We can click on the second option
Click the download menu
Set the language to simple Chinese
Then click OK to complete the installation
Then click OK to confirm to log in
This pop-up window is to remind you
How many days the software will expire
And the specific expiration date
During the trial period
You can click on the subscribe button below the date
To pay for it
Or when the trial period of the software is over
You still want to continue to use the Cloth software
You can come to the Chinese official website
In the price tag page above
Click to view the price plan or subscribe to the software
Click to confirm to close the window
After opening the software
If you need to switch the interface language
You can select the language in the top settings of the software
Switch
After changing, restart the software to work
This is the complete registration and installation preparation work
Next, go back to the Cloth Chinese official website
See the learning label above
There are tutorials, training camps, handbooks and community forums
First click on the tutorial
It will jump to the Cloth official Bilibili account
Here we will continue to upload the latest tutorials
And previous information
This course is a new entry course in the Cloth tutorial series
Can help Xiaobai easily get started
Quickly master the use skills of the Cloth software
In addition, we also provide two advanced series courses
Designers' specialties and master classes
If you have completed the entry course
Or have a basic level of Cloth
Can pass them
Further learn various advanced production techniques
Designers' specialties
Is designed for designers
3D design and production courses
From scratch
Wu Zhiyang in Cloth
Cloth clothing sample design
Also based on the basic model library
Change the design
And various flower design
Style design skills
And master class
It contains more products
Complex style teaching
Complex fabric advanced processing
And a series of exhibitions and scenes
Contents such as scenery construction and rendering
Suitable for everyone in a deeper learning stage
Or there is a special product type of production needs
View
In addition
We will continue to update some
Cloth's use of small technique videos
For example, how to wear a button
Connection advantage
Self-defined button and name line, etc.
You can choose to learn by default
Because the Cloth software has been continuously optimizing updates
So when the new version is released
We will also launch the new function series video at the same time
Help everyone quickly upgrade
And master the latest technology
Next
We specifically see the content of the new entry course
This course is divided into two stages
Currently released is the first half
The second half will be released soon
Suggest everyone to watch the learning once
First through Cloth Ecosystem
To understand the Cloth product ecosystem
By watching the course guide
Clear前置信息
Complete preparation
Then the third
The four small steps quickly enter the core tools
We will guide you to master Cloth basic tools
The basic process of 3D clothing production
The fifth small step material
Will focus on the explanation
The concept and application related to material analysis
In the sixth section of simulation control
We will add practical tools through the actual combat case
Improve your 3D simulation control ability
About the acquisition of course materials
Includes two parts
First is the Cloth file material
Related materials have been uploaded to Connect Business
You can download it directly from the Cloth software
Open the Cloth software
Click the blue icon in the upper right corner
Open the library
Switch to the Connect label
This is the same as our Connect online mall
You can use the selection option or keyword
To unlock the required materials
For the selected materials
You can right-click to enter the shopping cart
Or open it in the Connect web page
The second is the picture material
All the reference pictures used in the teaching
Will be placed in the network disk link below this video
You can directly click to extract
Of course, you can also use your own pictures
To create
In addition, we will also hold training camps on a regular basis
Provide customized courses for business users and university users
And senior talent classes for face-to-face public registration
Those who are interested can learn
In the learning process
If you want to know more about how to use the function
You can also click on the manual
To unlock the corresponding function instructions
Finally, you can also
In the learning menu at the top of the website
Find the community forum
Join our official exchange community
Welcome to discuss with us
Any problems you encounter in the use of software
Share your work
We will also hold fun activities and creative competitions
Various exquisite surrounding gifts are waiting for you
Looking forward to seeing you in the community